ksourcerer.org 2016-04-02

# Croatia hotel reservation – croatiahotel24.net – Privacy

### Privacy Policy

We take our responsibility regarding your privacy, very seriously. The information we request when making your reservation, is requested in order to offer you a professional service.

We will only disclose your personal information to third parties for the purposes of completing your booking through us, in order to provide you with the information or services you have requested, or with your explicit consent. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to certain permitted third parties including members of our own group, trusted partners some of whom are located outside the European Economic Area and our own professional advisers.

### Credit Card information

We will not charge your credit card. Your credit card information is only required to guarantee your booking. You will pay your stay at the hotel.

Your credit card information is sent to us through a secure server. We use the latest, most secure technology available, which encrypts all your personal and credit card details. The encryption method used is the industry standard "Secure Socket Layer" (SSL) technology. Our SSL certificate has been issued by Thawte.

Our server and network are protected by firewalls against unauthorized access. This means we can guarantee that it is totally safe to send us your credit card details. We will reimburse the first 50 euro should your credit card be misused or abused. The credit card company is obliged to pay the remainder.

Your credit card details will be kept until your arrival date at the hotel. After this date the details will be destroyed.

### Control over your data

You always have the right to review the personal data you have stored with us. Please state 'request personal data' in the subject line of your email.

If your personal data is incorrect, we will change it upon your request. You can also ask us to remove your personal data from its database by sending us an email to the same email address.

### When do we send you emails?

After you have made a booking you will receive a confirmation message with all the information about your booking. You may take this confirmation to the hotel as guarantee of the reservation.

Sometimes we may send feedback emails after your stay at the hotel. If you do not wish to give us your opinion, you can let us know and we wil not request any further feedback.

In the reservation process you can request our newsletter, which contains special offers and more information. You can also choose to stop receiving the newsletter at any time.

If you have any suggestions or remarks about this privacy statement, please send an email us.
